<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraBar</title>
        <item>
            <title>1.0</title>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 17:38:48 +0200</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>1</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>1.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>12.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-bar-updates/release-notes.html</sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[
                <h2>ExtraBar 1.0 – Your Mac, Your Rules, Your Bar! 🎉</h2>

                <h3>✨ Introducing ExtraBar</h3>
                <p>Welcome to <strong>ExtraBar</strong> – the customizable menu bar that finally gives power users the control they deserve!</p>

                <h3>🚀 Core Features</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>Two Display Modes:</strong> Choose between a sleek floating bar or native menu bar integration – whatever fits your workflow!</li>
                    <li><strong>16 Custom Action Types:</strong> Go beyond "Open" and "Quit" – run scripts, trigger shortcuts, make API calls, and more!</li>
                    <li><strong>Deep Links:</strong> Jump directly into Zoom meetings, Slack channels, Spotify playlists, and Notion pages with one click!</li>
                    <li><strong>36+ App Presets:</strong> Works out of the box with your favorite apps – VS Code, Figma, Zoom, Slack, Notion, and many more!</li>
                    <li><strong>Full Keyboard Support:</strong> Navigate and trigger actions without touching your mouse!</li>
                    <li><strong>Multi-Monitor Support:</strong> Seamless experience across all your displays!</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>💡 Perfect For</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>Meeting Warriors:</strong> One-click access to all your recurring Zoom meetings!</li>
                    <li><strong>Developers:</strong> Deep links to your 30+ projects – no more "recent items" limitations!</li>
                    <li><strong>Designers:</strong> Jump straight into your Figma files and design systems!</li>
                    <li><strong>Power Users:</strong> Automate complex workflows with scripts and shortcuts!</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>🎯 What Makes ExtraBar Different</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Unlike Bartender/Ice – we don't just organize, we <strong>create</strong> new functionality!</li>
                    <li>Unlike Alfred/Raycast – we're <strong>visual and persistent</strong>, always at your fingertips!</li>
                    <li>Unlike the native Dock – we're about <strong>using</strong> apps, not just launching them!</li>
                </ul>

                <p style="margin-top: 20px;"><em>Thank you for being part of the ExtraBar journey! We can't wait to see how you customize your workflow. 💙</em></p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-bar-updates/releases/download/prod/ExtraBar.dmg"
                length="4358404" type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="QgbhBXDM4aKfYhYW2Tyuv1rGmfT4CIQJf3dPMtBREuFtZnlFXT6XVH3MlMXZXJfXAxJFYhFCjDJsJkR34QMTDw=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
